

Skills

Graphic Design

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator

Video Editing

Vegas Pro, Adobe Premiere, Adobe After Effect, Davinci Resolve

Document Processing

Ms Office, LibreOffice, Zotero, PandaDoc, Printing, File Management

Web Development

HTML, CSS, SQL, Laravel, PHP, Hugo, GitHub

Task Automation

AutoHotKey

Interests

Designing

Film-making

Writing

Programming

Languages

Bahasa Indonesia

Expert

English Language

Expert

Anugerah

Graphic Designer

- A https://anugerah.netlify.app/

Summary

For nearly a decade, I have been creating original digital content on various social media platforms like YouTube and Instagram. My content includes digital art, films, and written pieces that I have produced both individually and in collaboration with others. I am confident in my abilities to create engaging and high-quality content that resonates with my audience.

Experience

Harat Inggris

01-29-2024 — Present

Vice President

Banjarmasin

An organization that focuses on the growth of the local community's English Language Development in Banjarmasin.

Lambung Mangkurat Debate Society

09-10-2021 — Present

Member of Media and Design Division

Banjarmasin

Working in Media & Design division, helped create a design for social media and organizational events.

Kalimantan Open Debate 2022 Event

12-15-2022 — 09-18-2022

Coordinator of Publication and Documentation

Banjarmasin

Division

Able to manage and helped coordinate team on their schedule and job.

ACC 2022 Event

12-25-2022 — 12-28-2022

Publication and Documentation

Banjarmasin

Shot videos, photos, and edit videos for documentation.

Regional Library and Archives Office

01-01-2020 — 01-03-2020

Librarian

Banjarmasin

Helped people to find, borrow, and return books. Managing archive data.

Education

Lambung Mangkurat University

2021 — Present

English Language Education Study Program

English Teacher

Vocational High School 4 Banjarmasin

2018 - 2021

Software Engineering

Software Engineer